{
    "id": "52fa759d31084186907671bde1ace2f7",
    "title": "Idiomatic expressions",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "1f21de21330141c58657382068d5e803",
            "title": "Idiomatic Expressions",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "His activities are always ……………….. suspicion",
                    "description": "If your actions are above suspicion, nobody will suspect you of doing something wrong",
                    "answers": [
                        "above",
                        "over",
                        "below"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "How are you going to account ........................... your absence at the meeting?",
                    "description": "To account for something is to provide a satisfactory explanation for something.",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "to",
                        "about"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The job interview was very easy and I am sure that I ................................ it.",
                    "description": "To ace something is to do exceptionally well in a tough situation.",
                    "answers": [
                        "clicked",
                        "aced",
                        "hacked"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The No-confidence motion was an .............................. test for the Prime Minister",
                    "description": "An acid test is a test where conclusions are beyond doubt.",
                    "answers": [
                        "acid",
                        "fire",
                        "sour"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ................................... a taste for ballet during her trip to Spain.",
                    "description": "To acquire a taste for something is to start liking it.",
                    "answers": [
                        "gained",
                        "earned",
                        "acquired"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Wages have increased ................................. the board.",
                    "description": "If something happens across the board, it is applicable to everyone equally.",
                    "answers": [
                        "along",
                        "across",
                        "through"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Her friend often teases her for not .................................. her age.",
                    "description": "To act your age is to act as a mature person.",
                    "answers": [
                        "behaving",
                        "acting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "That child has started acting ............................... again.",
                    "description": "To act up is to misbehave.",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "up",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The things that she said about your boyfriend do not ............................... to anything.",
                    "description": "If things do not add up, they do not mean anything.",
                    "answers": [
                        "add up",
                        "add in",
                        "add on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Dad advised me ..................................... buying a new car.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "against"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is afraid of his own .................................",
                    "description": "To be easily frightened.",
                    "answers": [
                        "shadow",
                        "friend",
                        "shade"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}